https://jfcs-stl.org/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | Jewish Family & Children's Services
Providing Compassionate Support &
Practical Solutions in St. Louis since 1871.Donate Newsletter Sign Up
Toggle navigation
About EventsEmploymentFinancial InformationPatient FormsPublicationsNews and UpdatesStaffClinical StaffBoard of DirectorsCOUNSELING
& TESTING Adult CounselingChildren & AdolescentSupport GroupsTesting & AssessmentChaplaincy with JF&CSSCHOOL BASED School Based ConsultationChild Abuse PreventionELDERLINK
ST. LOUIS Information/ReferralIn-Home Services/HomemakerOutreach/Gatekeeper ProgramChaplaincyHolocaust Survivor SupportFall Risk Prevention ProgramFOOD PANTRY ABOUT THE PANTRYLocation & HoursWho We ServeCelebration basketsDonate Food & Other ItemsVolunteeringFINANCIAL ASSISTANCECare Management Mental Health Care ManagementJewish Disability Care ConnectWays To Give Annual AppealTree of Life SocietyDonations2019 GalaLegacy GiftsTributes & MemorialsEndowmentTax CreditsCONTACT US
Toggle navigation
About EventsEmploymentFINANCIAL INFORMATIONPatient FormsPublicationsNews and UpdatesStaffClinical StaffBoard of DirectorsCOUNSELING
& TESTING Adult CounselingChildren & AdolescentSupport GroupsTesting & AssessmentChaplaincy with JF&CSSCHOOL BASED School Based ConsultationChild Abuse PreventionElderlink St. Louis Information/ReferralIn-home Services/HomemakerOutreach/Gatekeeper ProgramChaplaincyHolocaust Survivor SupportFall Risk Prevention ProgramFOOD PANTRY ABOUT THE PANTRYLocation & HoursWho We ServeCelebration basketsDonate Food & Other ItemsVolunteer at the PantryVolunteering with JF&CSFINANCIAL ASSISTANCECare Management Mental Health Care ManagementJewish Disability Care ConnectWays To Give Annual AppealTree of Life SocietyDonationsLegacy GiftsTributes & MemorialsEndowmentTax CreditsCONTACT USPrivacy NoticeThis privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for (https://jfcs-stl.org). This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request respond to your inquiry, e.g. to ship an order connect you with a service provider or to answer your question.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or our programs and services, or changes to this privacy policy.”Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (314) 993-1000 or via email at info@jfcs-stl.org.
Copyright © 2020. |
Privacy Policy | Jewish Family & Children's Service. All rights reserved. Site Designed and Developed by Thomson Printing, Creative & Graphics
